

About me

I am an empathetic control freak, a hybrid between art and technology. I believe it is the delightful details that make up a memorable design. I am also interested in games, VR, animation.

Contact

Portfolio: eloisechoi.com Email: eloisechoy@163.com/ eloisechoy.aiesec@gmail.com Phone: +8617610362607 (China)

Skills

Interface Design
Interaction Design
Research
Prototype
Usability Testing
3D Modeling
Video Editing
Project Management
Collaboration
Basic Programming

Toolkit

Sketch, InVision Adobe Creative Suite Maya, Unity, SketchUp HTML, CSS, JS, PHP Pencil and Paper

Language

Mandarin Cantonese English Japanese (beginner)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Game UX Designer | NetEase Games

January 2020 - present

Designed user interfaces for a mobile game, "Harry Potter: Magic Awakened" to fulfill new requirements proposed by Game Designers. Prepared ready-to-code in-engine prototypes which specify coordinates of each component using Cocos. Deeply collaborated with graphic designers, visual effect designers, engineers to ensure the final result meets the desired standard.

Visual/Interaction Designer | NOKIA

January 2019 - April 2019 (Co-op)

Designed user interface and experience for new features released on Nokia's software, from concept to mock-ups to pixel-perfect specifications. Researched and restructured complex technical data into feasible information architecture, considering its users and product strategies.

Course Visual & Interaction Designer | PwC

May 2018 - August 2018 (Co-op)

Designed interactive web-based eLearning courses and animations to explain business terminologies, expectations, and rules that distributed to 100,000+ employees. My role includes brainstorming, storyboarding, creating visual assets and development.

Graphic Designer | Intelli Management Group Inc.

January 2017 - April 2017 (Co-op)

Designed marketing materials including printing advertisements, email newsletters, and visual assets for various clients, following a strict timeline.

FREELANCE EXPERIENCE

Web Developer | TEDxSFU

January 2017 - Novemeber 2017

Redesigned the TEDxSFU website to communicate the theme of 2017 (Shift) and collaborated with teams of 11 directors to run the conference. My roles include ideating, wireframing, prototyping and developing using HTML, CSS, and JS.

Graphic Designer | BizField Angel Network

November 2017 - Feburary 2018

Designed brochures and developed a website to introduce the company and services using Wix.

EDUCATION

Interactive, Arts and Technology (B.Sc.) | Simon Fraser University

September 2014 - August 2019

Completed three co-op terms.